tecdoc.net 2018-09-04

# Data Privacy & Cookies | TecAlliance

at **  
TecAlliance GmbH**

## **General information**

We, TecAlliance GmbH, based in Ismaning, take protecting your private data very seriously and would like for you to feel comfortable visiting our website. Protecting your privacy when handling personal data is an important concern for us, which we take into account in our business processes. We handle data that is collected when visiting our website in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of the European Union.

## **Collection and processing of personal data**

Personal data is only handled within the scope of the applicable statutory regulations. This means that TecAlliance GmbH may collect, process and use your personal data (e.g. name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) insofar as it is required for the establishment, content-related arrangement and amendment of the contractual relationship with regard to the use of the website and the offered services and offerings.

Every access to our website is recorded for a limited period in log files in line with the law. This concerns your IP address, the website from which you are visiting us, our websites that you are visiting, as well as the date and the duration of the visit.

This data is exclusively used for internal purposes, i.e. for statistical purposes as well as to ensure the stability and operational security of the system.

TecAlliance GmbH does not collect any personal data via these websites insofar as you have not provided it to us voluntarily and submitted your declaration of consent in the corresponding place in the menu.

This personal data is only used for the purpose stated in the statement of consent and is deleted immediately after performing the respective service. The collected data is not disseminated to third parties (subject to a court order as part of a criminal investigation).

Naturally, you can withdraw your consent at any time in whole or in part with effect for the future with regard to TecAlliance GmbH by simply sending an e-mail to [ **dataprivacy@tecalliance.net**](mailto:dataprivacy@tecalliance.net) . We will then delete the affected data where not otherwise agreed with you.

## **Use of Cookies**

Cookies are files that the web server leaves behind on the computers of users for the purpose of tracking. We use cookies to facilitate repeated access and the use of our website for users. They do not cause any damage to computer systems and files. It is possible in most browsers to block the saving of all cookies, remove existing cookies and warn the user before a cookie is saved.

## **Etracker**

On this website, data is collected and stored for purposes of marketing and optimisation using the technologies of etracker GmbH (www.etracker.com).

From this data use, profiles can be generated using a pseudonym. Cookies may also be used for this purpose. Cookies are small text files that are stored locally in the temporary memory of the Internet browser of the website visitor. Cookies make it possible to recognise the Internet browser again.  
The data collected with the etracker technologies is not used to personally identify a website visitor without his/her especially given approval. The data is also not joined to personal data through the pseudonym.

Future data collection and storage can be terminated at any time with immediate effect.  If you do not wish to allow the storage of your visitor data, please click [**here**](http://www.etracker.de/privacy?sid=9cace9b7330d3648a4663b64c8c4ab78&id=privacy&et=V23Jbb&languageId=2).

## **Piwik**

Our website uses Piwik, a so-called web analysis service. Piwik uses cookies, which are text files that are saved on your computer to make it possible for us to analyse the use of the website. To this end the use information generated in the cookie (including a shortened version of your IP address) is sent to our server, where it is saved for the purpose of use analysis. This helps us to optimise our website. In this process your IP address is anonymised so that you as a user remain anonymous to us. The information on your use of the website that is in the cookie will not be given to any third party. You can prevent the use of cookies with the appropriate setting of your browser software. However, in this case you may not be able to use all functions of this website.  
If you do not agree to the saving and evaluation of this data from your visit, you can stop this saving and use by mouse click at any time. In this case a so-called opt-out cookie will be stored in your browser with the consequence that Piwik will not store session data. Note: If you delete cookies, this will also delete the opt-out cookie so that you might have to activate it again.

You can choose to opt out of being tracked by all marketing and advertising tools installed on this website. Please, click below to receive an opt-out cookie. In order for your change to take effect, please restart your browser!

## **Data Security**

Your data is hosted with a provider in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Both TecAlliance GmbH and the provider employ technical and organisational security measures to protect your collected data from accidental or deliberate manipulation, loss, destruction, and against access by unauthorised persons. Our security measures are constantly being improved in line with technological advancements.

## **Right to information**

On request, we will be happy to inform you, in line with applicable law, whether and which personal data is saved with us about you. Our contact details:  
TecAlliance GmbH  
Steinheilstr. 10  
85737 Ismaning

## **Changes to this data protection statement**

Please note that this data protection statement can be amended if new legal regulations make this necessary.  
Ismaning, 20th of April 2018
